Smells so good.
Smells good.
Is it hotpot?
Hotpot!
Hotpot! My spicy hotpot!
My spicy hotpot.
Let's go.
Smells amazing.
Smells good.
I'm already drooling.
Congratulations, everyone, on completing the Second Exam.
So, as a reward for everyone,
we prepared hotpot.
Let me give a thank you.
Thanks.
So you actually took Sun Mingyang's suggestion.
Thank you, everyone.
My suggestion was adopted.
I'm so happy.
That's amazing.
Okay, I'll guess.
He's going to play a game again.
So while everyone is eating,
we've also prepared for everyone
Hotpot Werewolf Game.
Help! We have to play a game.
We have to do it ourselves again.
In each round, among the eight players, there will be one Werewolf.
The Werewolf can use a specific action to attack others.
After the Werewolf attacks, the production team will wait a certain amount of time
to announce who has been eliminated.
I'll say, "Somebody, you're a out."
Then you can't eat or talk.
After "killing" three people,
review and vote someone out.
If it's a Werewolf, then the game ends.
If the Werewolf isn't voted out,
we continue the game.
After the Werewolf kills another person,
we'll move on to the review.
The Werewolf only needs to stay hidden until only two people remain, and then he wins.
If the Werewolf is voted out, the Villager side wins.
The Villager side will be awarded one point.
If the Werewolf wins, they get three points.
Let's hand out the role cards first.
It's you, right?
Alright, everyone close your eyes.
Werewolf, open your eyes.
Werewolf, confirm your action.
Okay, everyone open your eyes.
Let's serve the first round of dishes.
The game can start now.
Go easy on me.
Let us take a couple bites first, thanks.
I'm really getting a bit too hungry.
Is this supposed to be cooked?
This thing is cold, isn't it?
I don't know.
He said it's supposed to be cooked.
Right now, I don't dare to talk to anyone.
I can only talk to myself now.
I guess this crispy pork is probably supposed to be cooked.
Don't all look at me.
I just want to eat.
Guys, actually I'm the Werewolf.
I'm a Werewolf.
I am.
Okay, Jiang Xiaomeng, you're a out.
What?
Xiaomeng has been blocking here the whole time.
Come on, show humanity.
Why? He's always alone.
He's practically hiding himself away.
So do you think the Werewolf kills by making anyone
who doesn't speak within five minutes die automatically?
Come on, show humanity.
Because Xiaomeng is the only one who hasn't spoken.
Very likely.
And he hasn't made eye contact with anyone.
How did he suddenly get "killed"?
Why?
The luncheon meat is ready.
This is a gentleman's game.
I'm afraid I won't get any.
Jiang Xiaomeng, can you pour me a cup?
You're the only one I trust now.
What? I'll help.
I can only trust you now.
Ziyu, out.
Who contacted you?
Big Ma.
No, I asked Xiaomeng to pour it for me.
It's Big Ma.
When Ziyu was "killed",
I was watching them do actions to each other.
And Ziyu just got "killed."
Right.
Either Big Ma or Ruijian.
It's not me.
Why are you randomly voting people out?
It's so hot.
Not cooked.
I'll sacrifice myself.
Come on, Big Ma.
What did you say you want me to do?
Stand up.
Come on, stand.
Sit down, look me in the eye.
What else?
What instructions do you have?
You give the orders.
I command you.
Take a taxi home.
It definitely won't be that simple.
Stupid question.
Okay, Zhou Guorui, out.
Just now, Guorui and Mingyang
just did some gestures to each other.
If I get "killed" next,
Mingyang is the one who "kills".
Come on, whatever you tell me to do, I'll do it.
If I'm dead, it's gotta be you.
Whatever you ask me to do, I'll do it.
You stand up first.
You sit down.
Okay, I stand up, I sit down.
It's not you at all.
When the two of us did that action,
Ziyu just got "killed."
Before Ziyu was "killed", I hadn't said a single word to him.
But I can only say Sun Mingyang probably isn't.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have tried so hard to prove myself.
Because he was standing with Zhang Ziyu.
When Zhang Ziyu was "killed",
he didn't look over there at all.
I could see the two of them.
Right.
Maybe he was making a move.
Was it you?
What move did I make?
You didn't say anything just now.
But I just glanced at you,
and then immediately looked back.
Then I couldn't have killed you.
I think the suspect is now between
you and Ruijian.
I think it's Ruijian.
Then let's vote Ruijian first.
Let's vote. Come on.
Come on, three, two, one, vote.
Okay, Wang Ruijian, Out.
Game continues.
Are you guys dummies?
Why did you vote for me again?
Sorry, then it's Big Ma.
Don't have any contact with Big Ma this round.
It's not Weixian. I think it's Guanyu.
What do you think my motive is?
Your motive
is that you're the Werewolf
and you need to "kill" someone.
I have a feeling,
the next one should be me.
So the game has started now, right?
I know who it is.
It's okay, you guys discuss.
I've been watching Guanyu.
It's Guanyu.
Guanyu just did that to you.
Like this.
I did this to him.
But he wasn't "killed".
You then asked.
After you finished this,
you turned back and asked, "Has it started?"
I really trust you.
I've been staring at him.
I'm telling you, if he's "killed", it's Weixian.
I tell you.
Then I'll watch Weixian. I'll keep an eye on him.
If you get "killed", it's him.
If I get "killed", it's him.
Our eyes right now...
Okay, Chen Zhixuan, out.
It's Guanyu.
Weixian was pretty normal this time, even though he winked at me.
That wink was you.
You're putting on a show again.
Excuses. I'll give you room to make excuses.
I didn't.
I have nothing to argue about.
Hurry up and vote.
Come on.
Come on, Guanyu is number one.
Three, two, one.
Okay, Guanyu, out.
So, are you the Werewolf?
After I put my foot out,
whoever I point to is who I "kill."
What a smell.
Pointing at people with your foot?
Pointing at people with your foot.
That's really something, man.
Such a stink, such a stink.
How are we supposed to eat?
At the time, I thought to myself.
"Are you crazy? You're just having a meal, why are you taking off your shoes?"
Do you want to drink?
Can we have a little to drink?
I can understand you doing something this insane.
So how did you
point at me with your toes?
Come, watch me.
Step one, take off your shoes.
Step two, move your foot back.
Step three.
So creepy.
Don't show me your feet.
Thank you, Director,
for letting me have a meal.
I've noticed in this game, Werewolves can keep eating.
Right, I want to be a Werewolf.
I want to be a Werewolf too.
Next, I will look at each person's feet one by one.
Don't take off your shoes.
Come on, next round.
Things don't go as one wishes.
Don't "kill" me.
I want to eat a little longer.
Come on, everyone close your eyes.
Okay, Werewolves, open your eyes.
Okay, Werewolves, please confirm your orders.
Okay.
Werewolves, close your eyes.
Everyone, open your eyes.
The game can begin.
I'm guarding my brain and my tripe.
I'll leave it to you.
But this brain takes a long time to cook, dear.
But I'm afraid it'll fall apart.
Because everyone will keep stirring it around later.
But don't you have to stay here for ten minutes?
Sorry.
Then I'll...
Mingyang, be careful.
I'll prop it up here.
So it doesn't fall apart later.
What are you doing?
I'm watching your feet.
Be careful.
This round it shouldn't be feet.
Xiaomeng, eat this.
This is delicious.
Okay, Sun Mingyang, out.
Finally, I'm not the first one.
Don't look at me.
Look me in the eyes.
Why do you keep coming over?
I'll just sit here and eat.
What do you want? What are you doing?
When something is out of the ordinary, there's something fishy.
Okay.
The three of us are eating together.
Come on.
Even if we're not Werewolves,
we keep an eye on the two people next to us.
And one of you keep an eye on me, okay?
The production team is watching you.
Right, Xiaomeng, you keep an eye on me.
I won't watch.
So sad, so upset.
You'll kill me first.
I'm going to get some glutinous rice cake. Move.
I'll watch you bring the glutinous rice cake.
Just watching.
Once you grab some, come back.
Protect me, please?
Watch your back.
Okay, come.
Come back.
I want some glutinous rice cake too.
I didn't get any glutinous rice cake either.
You can just come over and feed me now.
Is it hot?
Is it really hot?
See, this is what happens when you break the rules.
Scalded to "death."
Weixian, don't look around.
Weixian, I'm watching you.
I'm looking at you.
When he's got something to hide,
he just starts keeping quiet and be like this.
I'm watching.
I'm watching both left and right.
I'll just watch both sides.
Okay.
Why hasn't anyone been "killed" yet?
Why is it so quiet?
Because the Werewolf has been "killed."
Okay, Zhou Guorui, out.
Not me, really not me.
I didn't make any moves.
Maybe I'll try this.
Do you think it's ready?
I think we can use the serving chopsticks for a small piece.
Yeah, you can have a taste.
Guanyu, can you help me cook some tripe?
Okay.
Okay, thanks.
I'm not getting "killed", right?
No, I really can't pick it up.
It's not that bad.
Come on, it's ready.
Then this one.
You eat spicy, right?
I want to eat tripe.
Xiaomeng hasn't been "killed" yet, right?
Thanks.
Okay, Guanyu, you're out.
I won't give it to you.
We can Review now.
I think it should be Ziyu.
Weixian.
Actually, I think it's Weixian too.
Because of his behavior.
He definitely wanted to frame me.
It wasn't me, why would I frame you?
Because I was just eating the whole time.
For these three rounds, I've been purely focused on eating.
I want to be a silent foodie.
The main thing is, I can't guess how he did it.
While eating, what other abnormal behaviors are there?
Some really disgusting stuff.
Anyway, I'd never in my life think of pointing with a foot.
Let's look at the actual situation.
I really didn't have any contact with Guorui or Guanyu.
But Ziyu had contact with Guanyu.
Ziyu had contact with Guorui.
Right?
I think it might be like this.
Because I know for myself what my own role is.
And then that Werewolf probably saw me make that move.
And he knew
I asked Guanyu to
get me a piece of tripe,
and cook it in the hotpot.
Then his next target
was on Guanyu.
So I think that person who is the Werewolf
definitely saw me do this action.
So I suspect
these two people next to me.
Xiaomeng and Weixian.
You two saw it most clearly.
I don't know if they noticed this action.
Anyway, because I was next to you
I had him blanch a slice of tripe for me.
This move might be
even more intense for you.
Let's vote then. Come on.
Three, two, one.
Okay, Ma Weixian, out.
Game...
Game continues.
Sorry, Big Ma, I was wrong.
It's not you again, is it?
How could it be me?
I was just eating the whole time. Didn't move at all.
Then it's you.
It's not me.
It's you.
Come on, look at me.
Look at me.
I'm keeping my eyes on you.
I'm not eating.
I'm not eating either.
I'm keeping my eyes on you.
I'm not eating.
I'll keep my eyes locked on you.
Come on.
Come on, let's stop eating.
Come on, I'm not eating.
Come on, I'll just stare at you.
We'll just keep each other in check like this.
Don't move anything.
I won't move.
Don't move your feet either.
Don't move your toes either.
Right.
Don't move your tongue either.
Don't move your eyeballs either.
We'll just stare at each other.
Neither one of us is the Werewolf.
You might be one.
I'm definitely not a Werewolf.
What if you're not?
What if you are?
I'm absolutely not a Werewolf.
Hurry up and "kill" someone.
I'm not a Werewolf.
Then who is the Werewolf?
I'm a Villager.
Can you hurry up and "kill" someone?
Those two are pretty funny.
They've been thinking about it for ages.
Those two obviously haven't been hungry enough yet.
Look at me, I've gone hungry for two rounds already.
Werewolf, can you hurry up and "kill" someone?
Werewolf, hurry up and "kill" someone.
Alright, let's keep an eye on the two of them.
Werewolf, give us a clean kill.
Whoever the Werewolf is, can you hurry up and "kill" someone?
So annoying. So tired.
Do you know why the Werewolf isn't killing anyone?
Because Ruijian has Ziyu restrained.
So now the Werewolf can't "kill" anyone.
It's you, right?
Not me.
Okay.
Who's framing me?
Who's setting me up?
Put your hands together for me.
Okay.
Stand up straight for me.
Stand up straight.
Okay.
Both of them think the other is the Werewolf.
Still haven't killed anyone?
Not me. It's really not me.
It's you.
It's really not me.
I'm telling you.
It's definitely Xiaomeng.
Why hasn't Xiaomeng "killed" anyone yet?
Right?
He's framing me.
He just wants to frame me.
Actually, it's you.
He just wants it this way.
Not me.
Then the two villagers are just there
deadlocked for ten minutes.
What were they even doing?
I'm already full.
Hurry up.
They're all full.
I'm telling you,
let me lay out a very simple logic for you.
If I were the Werewolf,
I wouldn't let everyone
see me having Guanyu serve me food.
You know?
Are you guys going to eat or not?
I'm a bit hungry, what should I do?
I'm a bit tired, what should I do?
I'm thirsty.
Actually, I think it's him.
He's the most honest one.
Hiding in plain sight.
He likes playing that hiding-in-plain-sight game.
You know?
So, we've been watching for so long
shouldn't we be sure by now?
You're probably not the one.
Yes.
Go back to your seat.
Who else wants in?
He's about to make a move.
I do.
Now let me tell you,
he's about to make a move.
Because now the two of us are back.
Careful, they're about to make a move.
Careful.
Okay?
How about we let the Werewolf
"kill" someone in peace?
Let him "kill" someone.
Let's end this farce quickly.
Don't touch me.
Xiaomeng, was the brain cooked just now?
Was the brain cooked?
I keep feeling like he pointed at me.
You haven't eaten yet.
Your thumb.
He pointed at me with his thumb.
Is it that if someone serves me food,
and I don't eat it...
Ruijian, out.
So then.
Xiaomeng.
Alright, remember your face right now.
So can we vote now?
Alright, vote.
Come on, three, two, one.
Ziyu was "killed."
Well, congrats to the Werewolves for winning.
Finally, a win.
You...
Let's switch places.
Ruijian, remember the face you just made.
So why are you "killing" the three of us?
At the time...
Do you know how difficult it was to "kill" anyone then?
The spoon goes in, and whoever it points to is out.
I put it over there because it's not handy for me,
so I can't "kill" that side.
You know?
So you killed the three of us first.
Because you're right-handed.
Right.
Quick, switch to your left hand.
So no wonder the bowl is completely full,
and you still won't eat it.
I was just saying,
after all that eating, the bowl is still full.
How much did you scoop out just to get us killed?
It even overflowed.
Didn't I suspect from the very beginning that it was Chen Zhixuan?
We're like clowns, us two.
We're total clowns now.
Then let's play one last round.
Guanyu and Ruijian each get three points.
Finally, congratulations to Zhixuan and Ruijian.
Became our
MVP of the Hotpot Werewolf Game.
We're partners.
We're partners again.
Okay, these two
have received a special reward.
Later, they can go out and experience a massage service.
Bro.
That feels so good.
Come on, combo move.
That hurts!
Who did that!
Didn't give me one chance.
Director.
Me...
Have some pity on me.
I've barely eaten two bites.
Can I go get a massage with them?
The remaining six can't just sit around either.
We have a set building over here.
Later, move our props over
and clean the place up.
No, bro, one more time. Come on.
Director, look me in the eyes
and say that one more time.
If you two dare go out,
don't you dare sleep in the dorm tonight.
Zhixuan, Ruijian.
The car is ready.
You can leave anytime.
One more.
Come on, you six, send off the two winners.
Thank you, everyone.
Thanks, everybody.
Thanks.
The two of them are going for a massage.
They might not be the ones getting massaged.
They might be going to massage someone else.
Thank you, everyone.
Good work. Bye.
Come on, Mingyang and Guorui, come back.
They really left.
They really...
They're really leaving.
They're leaving.
Come back, you guys.
You two, hurry back.
Actually, I just clap the slate,
and they'll come back, right?
Actually, is it that if I clap the slate and say "cut"
they'll come back.
You try clapping it.
Alright, that's a wrap for today.
Thank you, teachers.
Let's take a break.
Alright, prop box.
Then first, we need to
carry our prop boxes over to the set building.
Look, look at those two.
Look, we've won the competition now,
we're going to get a massage.
We've now won
the Hotpot Battle championship at noon.
We're going to get a massage.
Yeah, our reward is actually a massage.
You scared me, you know that?
So it's actually true?
Those six dummies are over here.
They're over here eating
the food we left behind.
Anything you want to say?
It's so amazing.
This is amazing.
Really amazing.
We've gotta record this
and show them.
Piss them off.
It's literally insane.
But it feels like it's gonna rain now.
You guys are actually going?
Really, bro.
You guys are really going?
Look at Mingyang here.
Anything you want to say?
Bye, bro.
Bye, I'll miss you.
I saw them get in the car.
Wait, aren't we in a show?
How long has it been since I had a massage?
Take me away, to the distant future.
What are you grinning about?
Hurry back.
They've all left.
They actually went off to have fun.
They told me if I drag you back, we can go get a massage.
What?
Don't you want to shoot another segment like "Adventure in the Massage Room"?